ADITI G

aditi78g@gmail.com

9986846795

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To obtain a challenging and sound position in a good company and work enthusiastically to achieve the goal of the organization with devotion and hard work.

CAREER SUMMARY

Total Years of Experience: 5.2 years (Since March 2019 to till date) as IIB/ACE

Developer.

NTT Data: March 2019 to June 2019(4 months training) July 2019 to January 2022 (2.11 years)

Cognizant: February 2022 to August 2022 (6 months)

IBM: September 2022 to till date. (1.7 Years)

SKILL SET

SOA Stack : IBM IIB (Integration Bus) V9, V10, ACE V12(App Connect Enterprise), Basics of API

Connect and MQ.

Languages : ESQL, Basics of Java

Tools & Utilities : SOAP UI, Jenkins, Bit Bucket, Postman, RFHUtil, WinSCP, MQ Explorer, JIRA,

Git, SVN

Framework : IIB

Protocols : HTTP, MQ, FTP, SOAP, DB

Message Formats : XML, JSON, DFDL

Certifications : IBM Certified Solution Developer- App Connect Enterprise V11

PROFESSIONAL RESPONSIBLITIES

- Experience in Designing, developing and testing IBM Integration Bus (IIB) v9.0, v10.0 and ACE v12.
- Experience in working with below IIB nodes:

HTTPInput, HTTPReply, HTTPRequest, Compute, FileRead, FileOutput, FileInput, MQInput, MQOutput, MQGet, Filter, RouteToLabel, Label, Input, Output, FlowOrder, RCD, SOAPInput, SOAPRequest, SOAPReply, Java Compute.

- · Strong programming Knowledge of ESQL.
- Designed and developed more than 60+ message flows.
- Experience with a testing tool such as SOAP UI, POSTMAN, RFHUtil and MQ Explorer.
- Extensive experience with XML, JSON, DFDL message parsing and transformations
- Worked under both Agile and Waterfall methodologies.
- Involved in development and testing of the IIB and ACE applications with Security Profiles.
- Worked on the requirement gathering, development, unit testing of Api's and published them in higher environments using API Connect Platform. Provided testing support for the same.
- Problem analysis and validation of classification.
- · Working experience with direct client

PROFESSIONAL PROJECT #1 (NTT Data)

Title: BMW CAN IIB receives retails/leads/parts order/repair order from multiple vendors, those requests need to be enriched/transformed/sent to downstream systems like repository, CRM and Vendors.

Role: Info Technology Analyst

Domain : Retailer CRM **Project Environment** : IIB 9/10

PROFESSIONAL PROJECT #2 (Cognizant)

Title : Enhancing the application based on the requirements of clients and providing

the fixes if any error reported in higher environment (CVS Pharmacy – Atena)

Role : Project Associate

Domain : Medical **Project Environment** : ACE

PROFESSIONAL PROJECT #3 (IBM)

Title : Migration of ESB applications from IIB V10 to ACE V12 (Canara Bank Project)

Role : Application Developer - EAI

Domain : Banking domain

Project Environment: ACE V12, Basics API Connect

GENERIC SOFT SKILLS

- Successful teamwork experience
- Proven the ability to transfer knowledge
- Ability to articulate and present different points-of-views on various technologies
- Experience in working with customers directly

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Awarded as "On the Spot Award" for supporting and wrapping up the project within a short span
 of time for a critical issue
- Awarded as "On the Spot Award" for working in multiple teams at same time
- Recognized and rewarded as a "Star Performer".

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Qualification	School/college	University	Year of passing	Percentage
B.E.(CS)	Vivekananda Institute of Technology, Bengaluru, Karnataka	VTU, Belgaum	2018	67.95%
PCMC	Seshadripuram PU main college, Bengaluru, Karnataka	-	2014	80.5%
SSLC	Max Muller High School, Bengaluru, Karnataka	-	2012	87.52%

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above-furnished details are true to the best of my knowledge and believe.

(ADITI G)